Marty Mann Papers
Marty Mann Papers
- Recordings
  - National Council on Alcoholism Annual Meeting & Institutes: "Modern Approaches to the Problem Drinker in Industry", 1960
    - Disc 12 [Luncheon address], 03/25/1960; mann_m_141; 12" phonodisc
      [Note in Album] Annual Luncheon / Introduction- Mrs. Marty Mann, Executive Director, National Council on Alcoholism / Address - Mr. Lee Hill, Assoc. Genera; Counsel, Humble Divison, Humble Oil & Refining Co.
    - Disc 13, The Community Approach, 03/25/1960; mann_m_142; 12" phonodisc
      [Note in Album] Annual Luncheon / Address - Mr. Lee Hill, Assoc. Genera; Counsel, Humble Division, Humble Oil & Refining Co. / Afternoon Session / Chairman - Philip R. Clarke, Jr., Manager, Industrial Department, Lehman Bros., Chicago -- Vice President, National Council on Alcoholism -- President, Chicago Committee on Alcoholism / "The Community Approach" - Laurence B. Ferris, Recreation Director, Corning Glass Works, Corning, New York
    - Disc 14, The Community Approach; The National Approach, 03/25/1960; mann_m_143; 12" phonodisc
      [Note in Album] Afternoon Session / Chairman - Philip R. Clarke, Jr., Manager, Industrial Department, Lehman Bros., Chicago -- Vice President, National Council on Alcoholism -- President, Chicago Committee on Alcoholism / "The Community Approach" - Laurence B. Ferris, Recreation Director, Corning Glass Works, Corning, New York / "The National Approach" - Yvelin Gardner, Deputy Executive Director, National Council on Alcoholism
    - The Community Approach; The National Approach, 03/25/1960; mann_m_076; 1/4" reel tape (Box 15)
      "Recording of the Annual Meeting on March 25, 1960 of the National Council on Alcoholism"
      [Note on Box] Address - Mr. Lee Hill, Assoc. General Counsel, Humble Division, Humble Oil & Refining Co. / AFTERNOON SESSION / Chairman - Philip R. Clarke, Jr., Manager, Industrial Department, Lehman Bros.. Chicago -- Vice President, National Council on Alcoholism -- President, Chicago Committee on Alcoholism / "The Community Approach" - Laurence B. Ferris, Recreation Director, Corning Glass Works, Corning, New York / "The National Approach" - Yvelin Gardner, Deputy Executive Director, National Council on Alcoholism "
    - Problem drinking in industry, 03/25/1960; mann_m_075; 1/4" reel tape (Box 15)
      [From inside box] Reel I side I / Melville D. Dickinsen - Chairman / Mr. Harrison Trice "Problem Drinking Today" / Henry C. Mielcarek "Inplant Program" / Side II / Dr. C. D'Alonzo "AA" / Francis I. Calonna "Industrial Clinic"
    - Disc 15, The National Approach, 03/25/1960; mann_m_144; 12" phonodisc
      [Note in Album] Afternoon Session / Chairman - Philip R. Clarke, Jr., Manager, Industrial Department, Lehman Bros., Chicago -- Vice President, National Council on Alcoholism -- President, Chicago Committee on Alcoholism / "The National Approach" - Yvelin Gardner, Deputy Executive Director, National Council on Alcoholism
  - National Council on Alcoholism, 1961
    - Speakers (Part 1), 08/22/1961; mann_m_033; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
    - Speakers (Part 2), 08/22/1961; mann_m_032; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - [National Council on Alcoholism] Annual Meeting, Cincinnati, 1963
    - Panel session Friday, mann_m_009; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      [From note on inside] / "ANNUAL MEETING 1963 / PANEL REPORTS: / I. Private Agencies: Traverlers Aid main concern, the homeless male. Family Service involved with total family problem of alcoholism. T. B. Association finds alcoholism boubles TB problem.
      II. Public Agencies: City; Administrator, enforcer, advisor and educator. County; political importance stresses demonstrations for local groups. Stae; no direct sevices, gives education and treatment demonstrations. Federal; Leadership in information and money to research to assessment of needs and filling needs.
      III. Clergy: Show alcoholic that he is not condemned but forgiven. Educate give hope and help to families as well. Changes of attitude due to: 1. Ecumenicity, 2. Interest of professions, 3. Rise of AA and NCA, 4. Expressions in public press, 5 New literature.
      IV. Law Enforcement (starts at very end of Side 1) / Concern must be in ALL groups, among ALL expert, also follow-up program vital. [ Isolated search aid: LEAD ] / L- Learn the Truth / E- Enable others to learn it. / A- Associate with those who can help / D- Don't give up!
      V Industry / Old, supervisor and new, trained staff member programs are described.
      VI AA - Al -Ateen reports and definitions
    - [Smithers, Mann, Grogan], mann_m_010; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      [From note in Box]
      Presentation to Mr. Smithers. Mrs. Mann Introduces Dr. Block
      Side I / Dr. Block gives excellent statement about alcoholism. This is latest of his talks and best for general audiences.
      Side II / Thomas S. Grogan Jr. / This talk is far to long and monotonous for general use."
      "NCA Annual Meeting Cincinnati 1963
      Side #1 / a. Mr. Smithers turns presidency over to Mr. Gulich / b. Mrs. Mann makes presentation to Mr. Smithers / e. Mr. Smithers Accepts. / d. Mr Gulich's acceptance speech / e. Mrs Mann introduces Dr. Block / d. Dr. Block
      Side #2 Thomas S Grogan Jr, Exec. Director Associated Health Agency of Cincinnati Area"
  - National Council on Alcoholism Annual Meeting: "Two Decades of Progress", 1964
    - Morning Session, 04/10/1964; mann_m_011; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Recording of Annual Meeting on April 10, 1964 / [Note on Box]: / Morning Session / Chairman / Selden D. Bacon, PH. D., Rugters center of Alcohol Studies / The Scope of the Problem / Mark Keller, Rutgers Center of Alcohol Studies / Research / Ebbe Curtis Hoff, PH. D., Medical College of Virginia"
    - [Ruth Fox, NCA, AA], 04/10/1964; mann_m_012; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Recording of Annual Meeting on April 10, 1964 at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel / [Note on Box]: / Treatment / Ruth Fox, M.D., National Council on Alcoholism / Alcoholics Anonymous / Representative, Alcoholics Anonymous"
    - Afternoon Session, 04/10/1964; mann_m_013; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Recording of Annual Meeting on April 10, 1964 / [Note on Box]: / Afternoon Session / Chariman / Harry M. Tiebout, National Council on Alcoholism / Official Agencies / Ernest A. Shepard, Connecticut Dept. of Mental Health / Voluntary Agencies / Yvelin Gardner, National Council on Alcoholism"
    - Disc 1, The Scope of the Problem, 04/10/1964; mann_m_145; 12" phonodisc
      [Note in Album] Morning Session / Chairman: Selden D. Bacon, PhD, Director, Rutgers Center of Alcohol Studies; Professor of Sociology, Rutgers University
      "The Scope of the Problem": Mark Keller, Research Specialist in Documentation, Rutgers Center of Alcohol Studies; Editor, "Quarterly Journal Studies on Alcohol."
    - Disc 2, The Scope of the Problem; Research; Treatment, 04/10/1964; mann_m_146; 12" phonodisc
      "Research": Ebbe Curtis Hoff, PhD, MD, Chairman, Division Psychiatric Research, Medical College of Virginia; Medical Director, Division of Alcohol Studies and Rehabilitation, Virginia State Health Department, Richmond, Virginia
      "Treatment": Ruth Fox, MD, Medical Director, National Council on Alcoholism"
    - Disc 3, Treatment; Alcoholics Anonymous, 04/10/1964; mann_m_147; 12" phonodisc
      "Treatment": Ruth Fox, MD, Medical Director, National Council on Alcoholism
      "Alcoholics Anonymous": Representative, Alcoholics Anonymous"
    - Disc 4, Alcoholics Anonymous, 04/10/1964; mann_m_148; 12" phonodisc
      "Alcoholics Anonymous": Representative, Alcoholics Anonymous
      Annual Luncheon / Presiding - Mr. R. Brinkley Smithers, Chairman of the Board, National Council on Alcoholism; President, Christopher D. Smithers Foundation
      President's Report - Mr. Merle A. Gulick, New York City "
    - Disc 5 [luncheon address and business meeting], 04/10/1964; mann_m_149; 12" phonodisc
      [Note in Album] Annual Luncheon / Presiding - Mr. R. Brinkley Smithers, Chairman of the Board, National Council on Alcoholism; President, Christopher D. Smithers Foundation
      Treasurer's Report - Mr. Austin MacCormick, New York City
      Introduction - Mrs. Marty Mann, Executive Director, National Council on Alcoholism
      Address - Mr. Wilbur J Cohen, Assistant Secretary, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Washington, D.C."
    - Disc 6, Official Agencies, 04/10/1964; mann_m_150; 12" phonodisc
      Address - Mr. Wilbur J Cohen, Assistant Secretary, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Washington, D.C.
      Afternoon Session / Chairman - Harry M. tiebout, MD, Member, Board of Directors, National Council on Alcoholism; formerly, Vice-Chairman, Connecticut Commission on Alcoholism
      "Official Agencies" - Ernest A. Shepherd, Chief, Alcoholism Dividision, Connecticut Department of Mental Health"
    - Disc 7, Official Agencies; Voluntary Agencies, 04/10/1964; mann_m_151; 12" phonodisc
      [Note in Album] Afternoon Session / Chairman - Harry M. tiebout, MD, Member, Board of Directors, National Council on Alcoholism; formerly, Vice-Chairman, Connecticut Commission on Alcoholism
      "Official Agencies" - Ernest A. Shepherd, Chief, Alcoholism Dividision, Connecticut Department of Mental Health
      "Voluntary Agencies" - Yvelin Gardner, Deputy Executive Director, National Council on Alcoholism"
    - Disc 8, Voluntary Agencies, 04/10/1964; mann_m_152; 12" phonodisc
  - National Council on Alcoholism Annual Meeting and Institutes, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1965
    - Morning Session (tape 1), 04/07/1965; mann_m_014; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Recording of Annual Meeting on April 7, 1965 at the Hotel Mayo in Tulsa, Oklahoma / [Note on Box] / Morning Session / "Introduction to Alcoholism" / Chairman - The Hon. Gerald S. Levin / "Effective Pastoral Counseling of Alcoholics and Their Families" - The Rev. John E. Keller / "The Social Agencies' Relation to the Problem" - Miss Marian J. Wettrick"
    - Morning Session (tape 2), 04/08/1965; mann_m_015; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Recording of Annual Meeting on April 8. 1965 at Hotel Mayo in Tulsa, Oklahoma / [Note on Box] / Morning Session / "Introduction to Alcoholism" / "Alcoholics Anonymous as a Community Resource" - Mr. John Park Lee / Afternoon Session / Chairman - The Hon. Gerald S. Levin / "The Council on Alcoholism as a Coordinating Agency" - Miss Mary Harkin"
    - Morning Session, 04/09/1965; mann_m_016; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Recording of Annual Meeting on 04/09/1965 / [Note on Box] / Morning Session / "Varieties of Industrial Experience" / Chairman - Mr. F. Forsha Russell / Introduction - Mrs. Marty Mann / Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Co. - Mr. J. Herb Larson, Manager, Personnel Services / Raytheon Company - Mrs. Willis L. Saulnier, Corporate Manager, Employee Benefits and Services / Kemper Insurance - Mr. Kenneth A. Rouse, Director, Rehabilitation Services, Safety Engineering Department / Afternoon Session / "The Total Community" / Chairman - Mr. William J. Sherry / "The Milwaukee Story" - Mr. James S. Ray, Administrator, Milwaukee Council on Alcoholism / "The Tulsa Story" - Mr. F. Morris Lookout, Industrial Representative, Tulsa Council on Alcoholism"
    - Annual Luncheon, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 04/09/1965; mann_m_017; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Recording of Annual Luncheon on 04/09/1965 / [Note on Box] / Presisding - Mr. R. Brinkley Smithers, Chairman of the Board, National Council on Alcoholism / President's Report - Mr. Merle A. Gulick / Treasurer's Report - Mr. Austin MacCormick / Introduction - Mrs. Marty Mann / Address - Mr. John M. Budd, President, Great Northern Railway Company; Member, Board of Directors, National Council on Alcoholism"
    - Tape #5, 1965; mann_m_019; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      [written on back of box] "Tape #5 / 4/8/65 -Tulsa / NAC OKLA / Ivory Room / 8 PM-9:30 PM / 3 3/4 / Membership Meeting, 5/5"
    - The Council on Alcoholism as a Coordination Agency; Working Together, 04/08/1965; mann_m_077; 1/4" reel tape (Box 15)
      "Recording of the National Council on Alcoholism Annual Meeting on April, 8, 1965 / [Note on box] / Luncheon / Speaker - R. Gordon Bell, M.D. / A.I.W. Awards
      Afternoon Session / Chairman - The Hon. Gerald S. Levin / "The Council on Alcoholism as a Coordinating Agency" - Miss Mary Harkin / "Working Together" - Mrs. Marty Mann"
    - Working Together; Varieties of Industrial Experience, 04/09/1965; mann_m_078; 1/4" reel tape (Box 15)
      "Recording of the National Council on Alcoholism Annual Meeting on April 9, 1965 / [Note on Box]: / Afternoon Session / "Working Together" - Mrs. Marty Mann (Concluded)
      Morning Session / "Varieties of Industrial Experience" / Chairman - Mr. F. Forsha Russell / Introduction - Mrs. Marty Mann / Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Co. - Mr. J. Herb Larson, Manager, Personnel Services / Raytheon Company - Mr. Willis L. Sauliner, Corporate Manager, Employee Benefits and Services / ?emper Insurance - Mr. Kenneth A. Rouse, rehabilitation Services, Safety Engineering Department "
  - National Council on Alcoholism Annual Meeting and Institutes: "Partners in Progress," New York, NY, 1966
    - Sharpening the Focus; Welcome to New Affiliates, 04/12/1966; mann_m_153; 12" phonodisc
    - Sharpening the Focus - Session; The Changing Image of Alcoholism, 04/12/1966; mann_m_154; 12" phonodisc
    - Sharpening the Focus; Challenges Facing the Voluntary Health Agency Today, 04/16/1966; mann_m_155; 12" phonodisc
      [same as mann_m_021]
    - Sharpening the Focus - Session Peter B. Hutt, mann_m_156; 12" phonodisc
      [From insert] Testing the Legality of Public Intoxication Laws as they Relate to Alcoholism: Implications for the Alcoholism Field"
    - Harrison M. Trice, 04/13/1966; mann_m_157; 12" phonodisc
      [From insert] Predictors of Treatment Success in a Follow-up Study of Treated Alcoholics. Harrison M. Trice, Ph. D., Cornell University "
    - Breakthroughs in Legislation, Harrison M. Trice, 04/14/1966; mann_m_158; 12" phonodisc
      [same as mann_m_022]
      [From insert]
      [side one] Predictors of Treatment Success in a Follow-up Study of Treated Alcoholics. Harrison M. Trice, Ph. D., Cornell University
      [side two, could be any of the following] Breakthroughs in Legislation Federal and State - Session / The California Plan / Arthur C. Hollister, M.D. California State Department of Public Health / The New York Plan / John R. Butler, N.Y.S. Department of Mental Hygiene / Team Tactics / Ben C. Liebermann, Jr.,, Tennessee Department of Mental Health / After Legislation, What? / Ernest A. Shepherd, A.M., S.T.B., Connecticut Department of Mental Health
    - Breakthroughs in Legislation, Harrison M. Trice, mann_m_159; 12" phonodisc
      [From insert] Breakthroughs in Legislation Federal and State - Session / The California Plan / Arthur C. Hollister, M.D. California State Department of Public Health / The New York Plan / John R. Butler, N.Y.S. Department of Mental Hygiene / Team Tactics / Ben C. Liebermann, Jr.,, Tennessee Department of Mental Health / After Legislation, What? / Ernest A. Shepherd, A.M., S.T.B., Connecticut Department of Mental Health
    - Breakthroughs in Legislation, Harrison M. Trice, 04/13/1966; mann_m_160; 12" phonodisc
    - Breakthroughs in Legislation, Harrison M. Trice, 04/14/1966; mann_m_161; 12" phonodisc
      [From insert] How the Atlanta Court Handles Chronic Alcoholics / Hon. Robert E. Jones, Chief Judge, Atlanta, Georgia / The San Francisco Court School for Alcoholism Prevention / Hon. Gerald S. Levin, Judge of Superior Court, California / A Doctor Looks At Chronic Drunkenness Offenders / David J. Myerson, M.D. Drug Addiction Center, Mass
    - The Courts, the Law, and the Alcoholic, 04/14/1966; mann_m_162; 12" phonodisc
    - The Courts, the Law, and the Alcoholic, 04/14/1966; mann_m_163; 12" phonodisc
      [same as mann_m_022 / mann_m_023]
      [From insert] The Courts, the Law, and the Alcoholic - Session / How the Atlanta Court Handles Chronic Alcoholics / Hon. Robert E. Jones, Chief Judge, Atlanta, Georgia / The San Francisco Court School for Alcoholism Prevention / Hon. Gerald S. Levin, Judge of Superior Court, California / A Doctor Looks At Chronic Drunkenness Offenders / David J. Myerson, M.D. Drug Addiction Center, Mass / Headstart for Recovery - Session / The Call Me Father / Rev. K.L. Sandercock, The Henry Ohlhoff House / An Experience Living / Mary Ann Larson, Beacon House, Inc. / The Utterly Impossible Project / Henry Jackson, St. Jude's House, Inc.
    - Headstart for Recovery; Headstart for Recovery; The Annual Meeting, Apr 1966; mann_m_164; 12" phonodisc
      [same as mann_m_023 / mann_m_024]
      "Headstart for Recovery - Session / The Call Me Father / Rev. K.L. Sandercock, The Henry Ohlhoff House / An Experience Living / Mary Ann Larson, Beacon House, Inc. / The Utterly Impossible Project / Henry Jackson, St. Jude's House, Inc.
    - [Current research], 04/15/1966; mann_m_165; 12" phonodisc
      [same as mann_m_024 / mann_m_025]
      [From insert] ANNUAL MEETING / What's Going on in Research - Session / Recent Sociological Research in Alcoholism / David J. Pittmann, Ph.D. North American Association of Alcoholism Programs / Psychological Research Relating to Alcoholism / Ruth Fox, M.D., NCA / New Aspects of Biochemical Research in Alcoholism / W.W. Westerfeld, Ph.D., State University of New York / Current Research in Treatment of Alcoholism / Ebbe Curtis Hoff, PhD., M.D., Virginia State Health Department
    - [Current research], 04/15/1966; mann_m_166; 12" phonodisc
    - [Current research], 04/15/2013; mann_m_167; 12" phonodisc
    - [Awards, introduction, address], 04/15/1966; mann_m_168; 12" phonodisc
      [same as mann_m_025]
      [From insert] Introduction of New President / Awards and Citations / Introduction of Speaker - Marty Mann / Address - The Right Rev. James A. Pike, J.S.A., S.T.D. Bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of California "
    - [Awards, introduction, address], 04/15/1966; mann_m_169; 12" phonodisc
  - National Council on Alcoholism "Partners In Progress," New York, NY, undated
    - [Tracks 1 and 2], mann_m_020; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Track 1 Tuesday / Sharpening the Focus-Session / Welcome to New Affiliates / Thomas P. Carpenter, NCA / The Changing Image of Alcoholism / Marty Mann, NCA / Challenges Facing the Voluntary Health Agency Today / Francis Wilcox, American Cancer Society
      Track 2 / Testing the legality of Public Intoxication Laws as they relate to alcoholism: implications for the alcoholism field / Peter B. Hutt, Covington and Burling"
    - [Tracks 3 and 4], mann_m_021; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Track 3 / Wednesday Evening / Annual Symposium of the NYC Medical Society on ALcoholism - Session / The Withdrawal State / Stanley E. Gitlow, M.D, N.Y. Medical College / Predictors of Treatment Success in a Follow-Up Study of Treated Alcoholics / Harrison M. Trice, Ph.D., Cornell University
      Track 4 / Predictors of Treatment Success in a Follow-Up Study of Treated Alcoholics / Harrison M. Trice, Ph.D., Cornell University"
    - [Tracks 5 and 6], mann_m_022; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Track 5 / Thursday / Breakthroughs in Legislation Federal and State - Session / The California Plan / Arthur C. Hollister, M.D. / California State Department of Public Health / The New York Plan / John R. Butler, N.Y.S. Dept of Mental Hygiene / Team Tactics / Ben C. Liebermann, Jr., Tenn. Department of Mental Health / After Legislation, What? / Ernest A. Shepher, A.M., S.T.B., Connecticut Department of Mental Health.
      Track 6 / Breakthroughs in Legislation Federal and State - Session / Thursday (Cont'd) / The Courts, The Law, and the Alcoholic - Session / How the Atlanta Courts Handles Chronic Alcoholics / Hon. Robert E. Jones, Chief Judge, Atlanta, Georgia. / The San Francisco Court Schol for Alcoholism Prevention / Hon. Gerald S. Levin, Judge of Superior Court, California / [cut off] ctor Looks at Chronic Drunkenness [cut off] enders / [cutoff] d J. Myerson, M.D. Drug Addiction Center, Massachusetts."
    - [Tracks 7 and 8], mann_m_023; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Track 7 / The Courts, The Law, and the Alcoholic - Session / Headstart for Recovery - Session / They Call Me Father / Rev. K.L. Sandercock, The Henry Ohlhoff House
      An Experience in Living / Mary Ann Larson, Beacon House, Inc. / The Utterly Impossible Project / Henry Jackson, St. Jude's House, Inc.
      Track 8 / Friday / ANNUAL MEETING / What's Going on in Research - Session / Recent Sociological Research in Alcoholism / David J. Pittmann, Ph.D. / North American Association of Alcoholism Programs / Psychological research Relating to Alcoholism / Ruth Fox, M.D., NCA / New Aspects of Biochemical Research in Alcoholism / W.W. Westerfeld, PhD., State University of New York"
    - [Tracks 9 and 10], mann_m_024; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      "Track 9 / New Aspects of Biochemical Research in Alcoholism / W.W. Westerfeld, Ph.D., State University of New York / Current Research in Treatment of Alcoholism / Ebbe Curtis Hoff, Ph.D. M.D., Virginia State Health Department / Introduction of the New President Awards and Citations / Introduction of Speaker - Marty Mann / Address - The Right Rev. James a. Pike, J.S.A., S.T.D. / Bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of California
      Track 10 / Address - The Right Rev. James a. Pike, J.S.A., S.T.D. / Bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of California"
    - [Track I and II], mann_m_025; 1/4" reel tape (Oversize 9)
      [From the box]
      "Track I / What's Going on in Research - Session / Recent Sociological Research in Alcoholism / David J. Pittmann, Ph.D. / North American Association of Alcoholism Programs / Psychological Research Relating to Alcoholism / Ruth Fox, M.D., NCA / New Aspects of Biochemical Research in Alcoholism / W.W. Westerfeld, Ph.D., State University of New York / Current Research in Treatment of Alcoholism / Ebbe Curtis Hoff, Ph.D., M.D., Virginia State Health Department
      Track II / Current Research in Treatment of Alcoholism / Ebbe Curtis Hoff, Ph.D., M.D., Virginia State Health Department"
  - National Council on Alcoholism Public Service Announcements, New York, NY, mann_m_170; public service announcements on alcoholism awareness featuring Jack Lemmon, and Mercedes McCambridge by the National Council on Alcoholism; 7" phonodisc
    [Side 1] 1- Mercedes McCambridge 60 seconds / 2- Mercedes McCambridge 30 seconds
    [Side 2] 1- Jack Lemmon 30 seconds"
  - National Council on Alcoholism Public Service Announcements, New York, NY, mann_m_171; radio public service announcements commissioned by the National Council on Alcoholism; 7" phonodisc
    [Side A] Cut 1 / Cut 2 / Cut 3
    [Side B] Cut 1 / Cut 2 / Cut 3 / Cut 4 / Cut 5 / Cut 6 / Cut 7
    Cut 3 on Side A features Luther A. Cloud, M.D., Senior Associate Medical Director, Equitable Life assurance Society of the United States and William W. Moore, Jr., Executive Director, National Council on Alcoholism. "
  - National Council on Alcoholism Public Service Announcements, New York, NY, mann_m_172; radio public service announcements commissioned by the National Council on Alcoholism featuring Del Sharbutt and Luther M. Cloud; 12" phonodisc
    [Side A] / Del Sharbutt / Cut 1: :20 / Cut 2: :20 / Cut 6: :20 / Cut 7: :20 / Cut 8: :20 / Cut 9: :30 / Cut 10: :30 / Cut 11: :30 / Cut 12: :30 / Cut 13: 30
    [Side B] Del Sharbutt / Cut 1: 1:00 / Cut 2: 1:00 / Cut 3: 1:00
    Luther M. Cloud, M.D. / President, National Council on Alcoholism
    Cut 1: :30 / Cut 2: 1:00 "
  - National Council on Alcoholism Public Service Announcements, New York, NY, mann_m_173; radio public service announcements commissioned by the National Council on Alcoholism; 7" phonodisc
    [Side A]